André de Paula Terceiro

Brazilian, divorcied, 41 years

Address: Rua (street) Doutor Eloy Chaves, 178 - bl. 5 - ap. 102 - Jundiaí- São Paulo - SP

Note: I can work in São Paulo and others cities

Telephone: (11) 98289-9112

E-mail: andreterceiro@yahoo.com.br, andrerapt82@gmail.com, andre@terceiro.com.br

Curriculum summary:

Data processing technician since 12/2001. I've been working with web programming since 2003, for example with Ruby, PHP, ASP, Actionscript (Flash), .NET (Visual Basic and a little bit of C#). Groovy and Javascript (including Node.JS) and Arduino. I use object orientation, MVC (mainly CakePHP, Code Igniter and Zend Framework, but I've studied others like Symfony), Ajax (via Xajax or directly with Jquery), visual effects with Jquery etc. I use template engines (various, depending on technology). In Flash I currently program AS3, integrating with PHP via XML or AMFPHP, but I've already programmed in AS2. The main types of systems I've developed are websites, administrative systems, various reports, e-commerce and

touchscreen multimedia for events (involving integration with external hardware, face detection via camera etc). PHP Brazil Moderator on Facebook until Facebook blocked my account without giving me a chance to try to explain myself. I made another account...

Goal:

Programming / systems analysis

Formation::

- Post Graduation in Software Engineering São Judas Tadeu University Completed in 07/2013
- Technologist in Precision Mechanics (Mechatronics/Robotics) FATEC. Completed in 07/2007
- Computer Technician (former data processing technician course) ETE Camargo Aranha. Completed on 12/2001
- Electronics technician ETE José Rocha Mendes. Completed on 07/2001

Certifications:

- CCNA Cisco (2002-2005)
- CCAI Cisco (Netacademy CCNA instructor)

Complementary courses and congresses:

- Various Meetups
- Arduino with Blender: MIS. Completed in 08/2009
- PHP Conference 2006 and 2012
- Linux IBTA systems and network administration. Completed on 11/2003
- Cisco Networking Academy. Completed in 2001
- Installation and maintenance of computers Senai. Completed on 06/1999

Professional experience

<u>Fixed-term projects</u>: May 2022 (current) Role: Senior devops programmer During this period when I was not employed under the CLT, I opted to work with PJ/cooperative members or in personal projects; - For Wabiz I programmed a bot for WhatsApp and a skill for Alexa. - Senior devops programmer allocated at Assaí by Decision: At Assaí I learned to work with "Low Code" platforms from Digibee and Automation Anywhere. I also made a system in Node.JS that integrated with DynamoDB and SOS. I use this TypeScript system, Jest for the tests (in addition to the Postman exported collections that ended up being used for testing too), the AWS SDK to integrate with AWS, I documented with Swagger, I made a very rich documentation in README.md etc. On the way I tried to achieve the goals, I even used my personal Amazon account for testing. It was one nice experience, but hiring PJ in most cases is to fulfill a goal specific, so I believe I didn't stay there long. I won't put many pictures, as things that are Assaí's intellectual property I must not share. At the beginning the requests were made with an authentication token via querystring, then passed to a variable of the headers, so Postman was even more useful, but we still had to test the testicles ourselves of request in Jest. - Self-employed: I did freelance work and solved personal things during this period - Devops programmer through Decision (another client): I worked allocated by Decision in a client (who they preferred not to reveal, so I won't). There in most of the time I moved in Jenkins pipelines, there was no time to stay until they migrated everything to Gitlab. depends on doing that I had to insert, if the information was in a repository, I would do the parsing in PHP. It was a nice place to work, I won't add any media because I felt it wasn't disclose some information. Note: I was not disconnected, I chose to leave there to work in another project

Riachuelo: from 06/2020 to 02/2022 Role: Senior devops programmer

Example of activities: I am a happy member of Riachuelo's center of technological excellence. There my role is to provide tools for the development teams to work with. I've worked for example with Lambda AWS, Jenkins, Node.JS and the programming languages Groovy and Javascript.

Self-employed while not in a company: from 04/2020 to 06/2020

Role: Senior programmer

Examples of activities: web freelances, tutorial recording, various software development

Swide: from 03/2020 to 04/2020 Role: Senior programmer

Examples of activities: I basically worked in an online bingo team.

I faced a new challenge at Swide. A big, ambitious, cool Project... I did a lot of things, for example 14

branches in 7 days, counting the time to learn the company's own framework.

I was hired for a project. Unfortunately the customer wanted to abort. I left with a feeling of accomplishment. That's why the time is short.

It was a nice experience.

Fundação Cásper Libero: from 03/2014 to 02/2020

Role: Senior programmer

Examples of activities: There is a link to my LinkedIN at http://www.terceiro.com.br. See there

please.

For professional growth, I faced a new challenge. In FCL programming was in PHP (using Wordpress, Zend Framework, Symfony and Laravel for example), Ruby, Phyton, Node (Javascript), Java and applications with Cordova. We took care of Gazeta Esportiva, Gazeta FM and AM, TV Gazeta and São Silvestre.

Promo Sapiens: from 07/2008 to 03/2014

Role: Systems Analyst.

Examples of activities: There is a link to my LinkedIN profile at http://www.terceiro.com.br. See

there please.

Below is a description of some works: e-commerce All Sell (http://www.allsell.com.br), multimedia for Samsung, Avon, Telefônica and Ideal Invest (more than 20, using Arduino, Visual Basic, Flash, PHP, touchscreens, face detection via camera, barcode detection, data registration, activation of

fluorescent lamps via Flash, multimedia synchronization on different PCs via network, etc.), Lig Lig website (old, administrative system in PHP, display data, AJAX, effects with Jquery etc), Hotma (old, http://www.hotma.com.br, administrative system in PHP, integration with Flash), system for generating email marketing for Ação Informática (system PHP administrative and HTML generation for triggering), administrative system and Flash integration for Promo Sapiens website (old), virtual poll and reports for Samsung, system for generating email signatures and inserting into email programs (Outlook, Thunderbird, Macintosh Mail etc) for di verses clients (formerly we used http://www.ff.rec.br/sim/assinatura_email/), interaction with sensors and LEDs for Telefônica (impact measurement via accelerometer and activation of LEDs through a microcontroller – Arduino's Atmega 168), Some things in Girafa's website (in "tableless" with Jquery) (http://www.girafa.com.br)

Grito Ateliê Digital: from 10/2007 to 04/2008

Role: Web programmer

<u>Examples of activities</u>: There is a link to my LinkedIN profile at http://www.terceiro.com.br. See there please.

Description of some works: website http://www.sabrinamatar.com.br/ - old version (modules for administrative system and front-end), Editora C4 website (http://www.editorac4.com.br) system administrative, data presentation, photo slide show), extensive research form for Sesi / Ação Educativa in 2008, e-mail marketing tool customization (formerly 2Send – the agency unfortunately is closed), tool customization for project management (Rolim Consult), administrative system and showcase for the Casa das Construções website (http://www.casadasconstrucoes.com.br/ - I don't know why they changed the website), various contributions to the website Conceiro Brazil (http://www.conceitobrazil.com.br/).

<u>Self-employed</u>: from 01/2005 to 09/2007 as main activity; since 10/2007 as a complementary activity

Role: web programming (PHP), maintenance of networks, servers and PABX;

<u>Examples of activities</u>: There is a link to my LinkedIN at http://www.terceiro.com.br. See there please.

The description of some works follows: reports for the Anuncio Certo site (old version of the site – the company closed), participation in the Names 2 Glue site (http://www.names2glue.com.br – the site was in Flash previously and not now,and I made the e-commerceof the website), changes on the Atrasorb website (http://www.atrasorb.com.br). For Torresan Eventos: administrative system and reports for registration of receptionists, forms and reports for research carried out in events, equipment maintenance, network and internal server.

TXT Marcom: from 06/01/2003 to 15/06/2004

<u>Role</u>: Web programming (PHP), maintenance of servers, network and PABX and internal support <u>Examples of activities</u>: There is a link to my LinkedIN at http://www.terceiro.com.br. See there please.

Description of some jobs: registration system for events and printing of identification cards on thermal printers, generation of various reports, internal systems, maintenance on Linux and Windows servers and internal support for users.

FASTDATA Informática LTDA: from 06/06/2002 to 12/15/2002

Role: Cisco Netacademy Instructor

Activity: Official Cisco Systems training (Cisco Networking Academy), preparatory to CCNA certification.

Cisco Systems (outsourced): from 02/15/2002 to 06/01/2002

Role: Customer service (Help desk)

<u>Languages</u>

Constant reading of various technical documents in English, intermediate in conversation in this language. I'm in Duolingo's diamond division.